

LUCIO BERTÉ



Junior FrontEnd REACT.JS Developer

EXPERIENCE

Go-Elevate | FullStack FrontEnd Developer Course

Apr. 2020 - Jan. 2021

Details

- Full stack developer course by Eng. Gustavo Andres Brey
- Using the Mumuki platform, which includes Computational Thinking, Gobstone.
- Object Oriented Programming, JavaScript, Git, Database, Linux, Slack, Github and React JS.

Scrimba.com | Advanced React Course

Dec. 2022 - present

Details

- Reusability in React, Performance and React Context.
- React Router and Dependencies.
- Ecommerce Functionalities.
- Redux

Ecommerce App | React FrontEnd Developer

Nov. 2022 - Nov. 2022

Details

- Responsive WebApp developed in React Js for personal use.
- Developed with Sidebar and reusable components, handling of React Router Dom, Forms with Email.js, Countdown Section with Imperative handling of Javascript.
- Management of Responsive Design for all types of devices.

Learn React Basics | React Developer

Oct. 2022 - Dec. 2022

Details

• Learned the basics of modern React by solving 140+ interactive coding challenges and building eight projects.

SOFTWARES & SKILLS

REACT HTML5 CSS3

JavaScript

Dependencies Management

Teamwork

PROFILE

Junior Front-End Developer Specializing in REACT JS Framework

Experience in coding web pages for personal and commercial portfolios, as well as specific functionalities such as creating a Login, or making HTTP requests using API's.

knowledge in Computational Thinking and Algorithmic Logic. Imperative, Functional, and object-oriented programming, database,

CONTACT

+54 9 223 5585610 (via Wpp)



Mar del Plata, Bs As, Argentina



Lucioaberte@gmail.com



in www.linkedin.com/in/LucioABerté

EDUCATION

Go-Elevate React Developer

Course by ing Gustavo Brey 2020 - 2021

Learn Basics About React

Course by Bob Zirrol at Scrimba.com 2022 - 2022

Advanced React

Course by Bob Zirrol at Scrimba.com

IDIOMS

English: Intermediate-High

Spanish: Native

Portuguese: Basic